I didn't notice anyone
chasing me,
so I think I'm safe.
This is me, Joey. This is Peter.
Where did you get this video?
In the alley in Purok Uno.
My uncle and I installed
the CCTV on the main street.
If you're hiding something,
now is the right time
to tell us.
Did you tip Major Delgado?
Golda?
I didn't even get a thank-you
gift for the tip I gave you?
Whose drugs did we intercept?
A name popped up in my contacts.
Executioner.
What are you working on
right now?
I'm planning to investigate
the drug transport
that was intercepted in Bolagos.
Miguel is a problem.
He's a block in our system.
In a chess game,
what do you do with a piece
that is an obstacle to the plan?
Knocked down.
Doesn't she look familiar?
I think I've seen her before.
Bingo!
We have another problem.
This.
What are you planning
to do with the video?
Don't tell me you'll post it.
We'll get there, but not now.
Do you need treatment?
I'm just here
to ask you something.
What is your relationship
with Major Miguel Delgado?
Found a body or a missing
person?
So far, there's none, Joey.
Usually, it's just kids
and seniors.
Why? What's the problem?
Who are you really, Mister?
And you too, Miss,
who are you really?
Okay, fine.
Okay?
Okay, Madam.
Madam...
Matias...
I'm begging you.
What do you need from me?
Didn't you say you couldn't
betray us?
Okay.
Let's prove your loyalty.
Where's his cell phone?
Hello, Ramon?
Major, we need to meet.
Where are you?
Here in...
Ramon!
Madam...
Have mercy, Madam.
Have mercy on my family, Madam.
Matias,
help me.
Madam, have mercy on me, Madam?
Madam!
He said he wanted to talk
to me,
but right now,
I can't contact him.
Something bad might happened
to him.
Your number cannot be completed
as dialed. Please...
Golda, this is Ramon,
Staff Sergeant Ramon Orbos...
Did your contacts mention
something?
Miguel, I told you everything
that I know!
I don't want to get involved
anymore.
Don't you want to get involved
because you're hiding something?
Why do you seem nervous?
There's another name mentioned
by my contacts,
and it's not Ramon Orbos.
So who is it?
You, Miguel.
You're on the syndicate's radar.
So be careful.
They will come after you.
It's dawn already.
- Where did you come from?
- Love.
I just followed up on a case.
Go get some rest.
How about you?
I'm not sleepy anymore.
I'll just follow.
Who is that?
What happen?
Joey...
Joey, the door, open that door,
Joey.
Joey...
Joey!
Peter?
- Joey, I'm outside.
- Why?
Open that door, open it.
Joey...
What is it?
Check this out.
Remember that guy you filmed in
the alley?
Make sure not to contaminate
the crime scene.
Okay, Sir.
Major, is the victim
a policeman?
That's Ramon Orbos, right?
One of the checkpoint
police officers
who inspected the drug-laden
truck that you intercepted.
He had injuries on his body,
so it looks like he was tortured
before he was completely
silenced.
Major, do you have any idea,
Major, who did this?
Major...
Do you know Golda Briones?
Here in the grassy part of
the Bypass Road,
boundary of Bolagos and Amaroso,
the body of a person identified
as Police Staff Sergeant
Ramon Orbos was found.
It will be remembered that Orbos
was one of the station police
who inspected the truck
that was seized
by the Bolagos Police containing
illegal drugs.
He was involved in Father's
drug bust case.
Isn't there a big syndicate
behind that?
Couldn't his death have
something to do with it?
It's possible.
Why?
I posted the video on FlipTok.
Oh my, Joey, are you serious?
Joey, it's dangerous,
especially since this happened!
What are you doing?
Major, do you know
Golda Briones?
I don't know her.
Weird, Major,
because what she told me
is so different.
What do you know about Golda?
She told me everything, Major.
Stay away from her.
Stop your investigation.
Major, I'm a reporter.
My job is to find out
and expose the truth.
Truth?
Is that really your goal?
Or is it just so you can say
something?
Stop bothering me!
Joey, what you did was so wrong.
What if that syndicate
tracked you down?
What if?
That's why I'm deleting it now!
Of course, I didn't use my real
account, right?
There, it's okay.
Even the account? Is it deleted?
Are you sure?
Yes, everything, deleted.
I also double-checked.
It's a good thing there
are almost no viewers.
You know, Joey, I told you
from the start
that you should have told
your father this.
Blunt force trauma to his wrist
and jawline.
Multiple contusions
and lacerations:
classic signs of torture.
But his cause of death,
single gunshot wound.
Contact range, here in his right
temporal lobe.
Approximate time of death?
Judging from rigor and lividity,
between 1 and 2 AM.
But, Sir,
there were no defensive wounds.
He was probably restrained
the whole time.
It seems Personal,
not just salvaged.
Agree, Sir.
Where are his personal effects?
- Here, Sir. Just a moment.
- Good.
Here it is.
Mother, I've been calling Father
for a while
but he's not answering.
You're not used to your Father.
You know you can't bother him
at work.
Just call him later.
What time is your class?
I don't have class today.
I'm going home.
I need to talk to Father.
Why, Joey? Did something happen?
I'll tell you later, Mother,
when I get there.
I'll update you
when I'm on the bus, Mother.
Okay. Be careful, my child,
okay? Love you.
I love you.
Come in.
Sir.
Sit down.
Sir, you called for me.
I also wanted to report
something to you.
Sergeant Orbos' preliminary
autopsy is out.
He had multiple blunt traumas.
He also had a gunshot wound
to the head,
at close range.
Execution style.
This is not the work
of amateurs.
Someone used enhanced
interrogation tactics
before he was completely
silenced.
His personal belongings were
also recovered
including his cell phone.
Hello, Ramon?
Major, we need to meet.
Where are you?
Where were you between 1 to 2 AM
last night, Major Delgado?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm near the bus station,
Mother.
Good morning, Ma'am.
Has anyone updated your CCTV
system?
System update?
That's not from the village.
That's personal use.
We installed that for
our bakery.
Andrew.
Final cue.
Are we dropping the expose
today?
Let's burn it.
Copy.
Kyle, standby.
And...
we are live in five, four,
three. Music up. Two...
Fellow Tirada, let's not play
around the bush anymore.
Let's get straight
to the agenda.
You all remember the Bolagos
drug bust operation, right?
P800 million pesos worth
of illegal narcotics
were intercepted.
Heroic work, some people say.
But now that Staff Sergeant
Ramon Orbos is dead,
tortured and executed,
the smell is even more pungent.
Here's a kicker.
We may have another cop
on the take,
a high-ranking one.
Major Miguel Delgado.
Is he really a hero or just
greedy for money?
Father?
- Father?
- Joey.
Mother...
Your father is still not home.
He still doesn't answer
my calls.
Maybe he's just busy
at the station or somewhere.
Wait a minute,
have you eaten yet?
I'll just prepare food for you.
Wait a minute, okay?
Just sit there.
Peter?
Hello? Joey, are you home
already?
Yes, I just got home. Why?
I've been reading about
drug bust cases in Bolagos.
I've heard reports and read
about your father, Joey.
You need to see this.
I'll send you the link.
Okay.
Major Miguel Delgado.
Yes, he was the one who ended
the controversial drug bust
operation in Bolagos.
Great, right?
But is he really a hero?
Is he the clean cop he claims
to be?
Or is he also a member
of the syndicate
and just pretending to be
a Saint?
These are not fake, Fellow
Tiradas.
These are not AI-generated.
Do you see this girl right here?
Her name is Golda Briones.
She herself confirmed to me
about her secret affair
with Major Delgado.
Why does Major Delgado know the
details of the drug shipments?
Because he is the protector
of the syndicate.
And once he gets that
protection money,
he will double-cross them.
That's the kind of cop
Major Delgado is.
A traitor, a crook,
and an immoral person.
Mother, let's not watch this
anymore.
There's no truth to what he's
saying.
And how can you believe it?
If that's true,
we should have been rich
for a long time now.
And this Andrew Dizon,
he's just mad at the police.
Did you know? At school,
he insulted Father.
Mother, maybe we should
just wait for Father
because I'm sure he has an
explanation for what's going on.
There's nothing clearer
than the photos I saw, Joey.
Your Father is fooling us.
Hey, hey!
Are you really not going
to stop lying?
This is for you.
You are placed under preventive
suspension
pending full investigation.
Have you shown your Father
the video
of the police officer
who was killed?
You know, I'm sure your Father
will find a way
so you'll be complete again.
I'm sure.
Good morning.
We need to recover a recorded
video.
Peter, who updated the systems
in Purok Uno?
It looks like the clean-up
was selective.
Something is being hidden,
and something is being erased.